{
    "subject": "resource/Meantime_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "English",
    "human_readable": "The language of Meantime (film) is English.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8881166577339172,
            "question": "What language is the film Meantime spoken in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7418694496154785,
            "question": "Is 'Meantime' a foreign language film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7081911563873291,
            "question": "Are there any dialects or accents used in the English spoken in 'Meantime'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6545724272727966,
            "question": "How does the use of English in 'Meantime' compare to other films set in the same era?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5961246490478516,
            "question": "Would someone who only speaks English understand 'Meantime'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5511884093284607,
            "question": "What other films have been made in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4190745949745178,
            "question": "Does the language of 'Meantime' contribute to its overall theme?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4030438959598541,
            "question": "Could 'Meantime' have been made more impactful by using a different language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23220911622047424,
            "question": "Are there any subtitles available for 'Meantime'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1393517404794693,
            "question": "What is the significance of language in film storytelling in general?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of Meantime (film) is English.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9161_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any subtitles available for 'Meantime'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9161_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could 'Meantime' have been made more impactful by using a different language?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9161_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the language of 'Meantime' contribute to its overall theme?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9161_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9161_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9161_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9161_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9161_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9161_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9161_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9161_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9161_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9161_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9161_57.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information mentions that the film \"Meantime\" features characters speaking and actors performing in English, which supports the statement that the language of the film is English."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}